- 嘿  - 嘿  你不是一直说
- Hey. - Hey. You keep saying
想做点亲密的事么
you want to do couple-y things
现在我们都正式喜欢对方了
now that we're officially in like?
呃  其实一直是你在这么说
Well, it's mostly been you that's been saying that,
但是你说话的样子好可爱  继续吧
but you're really cute when you talk, so continue.
那好  我报名参加舞蹈课了
Well, I signed us up for dance lessons.
噢
Ooh.
这挺浪漫的啊
That could be romantic.
哪一种舞  萨尔萨  探戈  华尔兹
What kind? Salsa, tango, waltz?
霹雳舞
Breakdancing!
Breakdancing?
对
Yeah.
呃  迪吉  这一点都不亲密
Um, Diggie, that's not couple-y.
噢  小玛  你大错特错了
Oh, mads, you're so wrong.
我做人浪的时候你刚好能接上
My wave could connect right to your wave.
咋样
What!
啊  做人浪啊
Ah, chain wave.
我也来掺和掺和
Give me some of that.
抱歉了  伙计们  我对霹雳舞很不感冒
Sorry, guys. Breaking's just not really my thing.
真不敢相信我们是同一对父母生的
It's hard to believe we're even related.
呃  嘿  我有个主意
Um, well... hey, here's an idea.
你们俩看起来对霹雳舞这么感兴趣
You guys both seem really excited about this,
为什么不一起上课呢
so why don't you take the lessons together?
然后迪吉嘛 你和我还可以找找有什么我们俩都爱干的事
And then Diggie, you and I can figure out something that we both want to do.
我们现在就是霹雳舞好兄弟了
We are breaking bros now.
做人浪吧
Chain wave.
好  好  做的真不错
Yeah yeah, that was nice.
让你们看看我的动作吧
Now let me show you my wave.
再见了
Buh-bye.